own3d.tv 2009-12-07

# own3D - Privacy Policy

**own3D Entertainment GmbH Privacy Notice**

The Privacy Policy describes how own3D and its subsidiaries treat personal information when you use own3D services, including information provided when you use own3D . In addition, the following describes privacy practices specific to own3D . To understand how we treat the information you give us as you use own3D , you should read this policy.   

You can watch videos on own3D without having an own3D Account. You can also contact us about a particular video without having an own3D Account.   

**Account-Related Activity:**

Certain other activities on own3D - like uploading videos, posting comments, flagging videos or watching restricted videosrequire you to have an own3D Account. We ask for some personal information when you create an own3D Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorised access.   

We may record information about your usage, such as when you use own3D , the channels, groups and favourites you subscribe to, the contacts you communicate with, the videos you watch and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in own3D (including UI elements, settings and other information). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.   

Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. 

  * If you submit personally identifiable information to us through 

    the own3D Sites, we use your personal information to operate, 

    maintain and provide to you the general and personalised features 

    and functionality of the own3D Sites and to process any flagging 

    activity or correspondence you send to us. 

  * Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other 

    users when you upload videos or send messages through the own3D 

    Sites and other users can contact you through messages and 

    comments. Any videos that you submit to the own3D Sites may be 

    redistributed through the Internet and other media channels and 

    may be viewed by the general public. If you have enabled active 

    sharing, other users may see that you, as identified by your 

    account name (not your email address), are watching the same video. 

  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable 

    information to send commercial or marketing messages without your 

    consent or except as part of a specific programme or feature for 

    which you will have the ability to opt in or opt out. We may, 

    however, use your email address without further consent for 

    non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of 

    major own3D Site changes or for customer service purposes). 

  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain 

    non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous user 

    usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, 

    etc.) to improve the quality and design of the own3D Sites and to 

    create new features, promotions, functionality and services by 

    storing, tracking, analysing and processing user preferences and 

    trends, as well as user activity and communications. 

  * We use cookies, clear gifs and log file information to: (a) store 

    information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your 

    visit or the next time you visit the own3D Sites; (b) provide 

    custom, personalised content and information; (c) monitor the 

    effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate 

    metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and 

    (e) track your entries, submissions and status in promotions, 

    sweepstakes and contests. If you download the own3D uploader, your 

    copy of the uploader includes a unique application number. The 

    unique application number and information about your installation 

    of the uploader (e.g. version number, language) will be sent to 

    own3D when the uploader automatically checks for updates. 

**Information That is Publicly Available**

  * When you create an account on the site, some information regarding 

    your account and your account activity will be provided to other 

    Users of the site. This may include the date you opened your 

    account, the date you last logged in to your account, your age (if 

    you choose to make it public), your country and the number of 

    videos you have watched. 

  * Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other 

    Users when you engage in certain activity on the site, such as 

    uploading videos or sending messages via the own3D Sites. Other 

    Users can contact you via messages and comments. 

  * You can also choose to add personal information that will be 

    visible to other Users on your channel page (the public facing 

    page for your account on the site). This may include a profile 

    picture, your name, gender, relationship status or other details. 

  * If you choose to add certain features to your channel page, these 

    features and your activity associated with these features will be 

    displayed to other Users and may be aggregated and shared with 

    your confirmed friends or other Users. Such shared activity may 

    include videos you add as favourites, videos you rate and videos 

    you have uploaded. 

  * Any videos that you submit to the own3D Sites may be redistributed 

    through the Internet and other media channels and may be viewed by 

    the general public. If you have enabled active sharing, other 

    users may see that you, as identified by your account name (not 

    your email address), are watching the same video. 

  * You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable 

    information through the own3D Sites, in which case you can still 

    view videos and explore the own3D Sites, but own3D may not be able 

    to provide certain services to you. Some advanced own3D features 

    may, for authentication purposes, require you to sign up. The 

    privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal 

    information associated with them. 

  * You may update or correct your personal profile information and 

    email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. 

  * You can control the information that is available to other Users 

    and your confirmed friends at any time, by editing your account 

    and the features included on your channel page. 

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites**

own3D allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the own3D Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the own3D Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalise the advertising content you see.   

own3D does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific programme or feature for which you will have the ability to opt in or opt out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks own3D to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men aged 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men aged 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the own3D Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.   

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt out of certain practices. own3D 's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers, which is subsequently shared with own3D , is maintained and handled by own3D in accordance with this privacy policy.
